Guide to the Duke University Union Records, 1954-ongoing UA.09.13.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- General Records1954-ongoing, 54 boxes
  - University Union Board Policy Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 22)
  - Major Attractions, 1983-1984 (Box 22)
  - Galleries Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 22)
  - Programming Council/Executive Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 22)
  - Programming for University Bars, 1983-1984 (Box 22)
  - Executive Committee: Minutes, 1983-1984 (Box 22)
  - Finance Committee: Members and Memoranda, 1983-1984 (Box 22)
  - Union Board Members, 1983-1984 (Box 22)
  - Ray Stark Film Festival, April 4-6, 1983 (Box 22)
  - Union Privilege Cards, 1983-1984 (Box 22)
  - Special Events Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 22)
  - Interaction Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 22)
  - Union Board: Budget, 1983-1984 (Box 22)
  - MCA Scholarship: General Records, 1983-1984 (Box 22)
  - Performing Arts Brochure, 1983-1984 (Box 22)
  - Retreats, 1983-1984 (Box 22)
  - Facilities Committee: Old Files, 1983-1984 (Box 22)
  - Programming Council, 1983-1984 (Box 22)
  - Galleries Committee: Insurance, 1983-1984 (Box 22)
  - Galleries Committee: General Records, circa 1983 (Box 22)
  - Special Events Committee: Folk Festival, September 30, 1983 (Box 22)
  - Special Events Committee: Holiday Celebration, December 1, 1983 (Box 22)
  - Special Events Committee: Springfest 1984, April 6-7, 1984 (Box 22)
  - Programming for University Bars: Correspondence, circa 1983-1984 (Box 22)
  - Programming for University Bars: Bands, 1983-1984 (Box 22)
  - Galleries Committee: Exhibitions, 1985 (Box 22)
  - Retreats, 1979-1985 (Box 22)
  - Programming Committee: Agendas/Minutes, 1984-1985 (Box 22)
  - Executive Board, 1984-1985 (Box 22)
  - Cable 13: Cable Van, 1985 (Box 22)
  - Cable 13: Yearlook, 1984-1985 (Box 22)
  - Cable 13: Video and Film Production, 1984 (Box 22)
  - Cable 13: Telecommunications, 1984 (Box 22)
  - Cable 13: Equipment Needs, 1984 (Box 22)
  - Cable 13: Cable Cast Football, 1984 (Box 22)
  - Cable 13: AT&T Information Systems, 1984 (Box 22)
  - UUB Meetings, 1983-1985 (Box 22)
  - Galleries Committee: Jackie Schuman, circa 1984 (Box 22)
  - Galleries Committee: Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 22)
  - Stillwater Films, "The April of Her Prime", 1984-1985 (Box 22)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Torch Song Trilogy, December 3-4, 1984 (Box 22)
  - Program Authorization Forms, 1984-1985 (Box 22)
  - Galleries Committee: General Records, 1984-1985 (Box 22)
  - Photographs: Correspondence, circa 1985 (Box 22)
  - Leadership Program, 1985 (Box 22)
  - Financial Report, March 14, 1985 (Box 22)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Southern Arts Federation, circa 1984-1985 (Box 22)
  - Interation Committee: Correspondence; Arts Day, 1984-1985 (Box 22)
  - ACUCAA: Miscellaneous Records, 1985 (Box 22)
  - Summer Programming, 1985 (Box 22)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Budget, 1984-1985 (Box 22)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Celeste Holm, "Hay Fever", circa 1984 (Box 22)
  - East Campus Center, 1984-1985 (Box 22)
  - Executive Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 22)
  - GPSC Orientation Speech, 1985 (Box 22)
  - The Killing Fields, 1984-1985 (Box 22)
  - Spring Retreat, 1985 (Box 22)
  - Galleries Committee: Charlotte Hastings, January, 1985 (Box 22)
  - Galleries Committee: Center Gallery, January, 1985 (Box 22)
  - Pinehurst Industries, 1985 (Box 22)
  - Galleries Committee: Marlene Loznicka, April, 1985 (Box 22)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Les Contes Paysans, November 11, 1984 (Box 22)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Ain't Misbehavin', March 11, 1985 (Box 22)
  - University Union Administrative Records, circa 1984-1985 (Box 22)
  - Finance: Budget, 1984-1985 (Box 22)
  - Union Feud, 1984 (Box 22)
  - Leadership Information, circa mid-1980s (Box 22)
  - Privilege Card Ads, 1984-1985 (Box 22)
  - Privilege Cards, 1984-1985 (Box 22)
  - Finance Meetings, etc., 1985 (Box 22)
  - Programming for University Bars (PUB), 1984-1985 (Box 22)
  - Union Board, 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - Union Booklet, 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - Duke/Durham Day, 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - Retreat, Fall 1984 (Box 23)
  - Facilities Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - Facilities Committee: Memoranda and Actions, 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - Facilities Committee: Financial Information, 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - Facilities Committee: Minutes, 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - Facilities Committee: Inspection Reports, 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - Executive and Facilities Committees: Minutes, 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - Special Events Committee: Tommy Dorsey, November 10, 1984 (Box 23)
  - Special Events, 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - Special Events Committee: Craft Fair, October 5, 1984 (Box 23)
  - Special Events Committee: Tree Lighting, 1984 (Box 23)
  - Special Events Committee: Springfest, March 29-30, 1985 (Box 23)
  - Program Council: Minutes, 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - Galleries Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - Interaction Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - DUU Officers and Committee Chairmen, 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - University Union Board Correspondence and Minutes, 1984 (Box 23)
  - Budget, 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - Constitutions, 1975, 1979, 1980, 1982, 1985 (Box 23)
  - Policy, 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - Policy Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - Bryan Center Policy Manual, 1985-1986 (Box 23)
  - Paul Young, 1985-1986 (Box 23)
  - The Hooters, 1985-1986 (Box 23)
  - Facilities Committee: Office Walls and Doors in Bryan Center, 1985-1986 (Box 23)
  - Facilities Committee: Inspection Reports, 1985-1986 (Box 23)
  - Facilities Committee: Inspection Reports and Key Deposits, 1985-1986 (Box 23)
  - Facilities Committee: BP Café Committee (Food Service Privatization), circa 1985 (Box 23)
  - Facilities Committee: BP Report - Copies, circa 1985 (Box 23)
  - Facilities Committee: Bryan Center Chairs and Locations, 1985-1986 (Box 23)
  - Programming Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 23)
  - Galleries Committee: Margaret Prentice, August, 1985 (Box 23)
  - Galleries Committee: Margot Richter, September, 1985 (Box 23)
  - Galleries Committee: Jimmy Crawford, October, 1985 (Box 23)
  - Galleries Committee: Martha Heine, October, 1985 (Box 23)
  - Galleries Committee: Roger Manley, November, 1985 (Box 23)
  - Galleries Committee: Sally Swenson, December, 1985 (Box 23)
  - Galleries Committee: Carol Barton, March, 1986 (Box 23)
  - Galleries Committee: Robin Surratt, April, 1986 (Box 23)
  - Galleries Committee: Elaine Blatt, April-May, 1986 (Box 23)
  - Galleries Committee: Diana Parrish Cull and Mary Moor Winnett, 1985-1986 (Box 23)
  - Galleries Committee: Artists Resumes - Rejected, 1985-1986 (Box 23)
  - Galleries Committee: General Materials, 1985-1986 (Box 23)
  - Galleries Committee: Ralph Ihrie, Summer 1986 (Box 23)
  - Vendor Policy, 1984-1986 (Box 23)
  - Fall Retreat, 1985 (Box 23)
  - Policy/PC/FAC Minutes, 1985-1986 (Box 23)
  - Lincoln Award, 1985-1986 (Box 23)
  - Finance Meeting Information, 1986 (Box 23)
  - Budget, 1985-1986 (Box 23)
  - Budget Proposal, 1985-1986 (Box 23)
  - PUB (Programming for University Bars), 1985-1986 (Box 23)
  - Miscellaneous Records, 1985-1986 (Box 23)
  - University Union Board, 1985-1986 (Box 23)
  - Executive Board, 1985-1986 (Box 23)
  - Letter Copies, 1985-1986 (Box 23)
  - NACA, 1985 (Box 23)
  - Completed Programming Forms, 1985-1986 (Box 23)
  - Programming: Minutes, 1985-1986 (Box 23)
  - Alcohol Policy, 1985-1986 (Box 23)
  - Facility Information, 1985-1986 (Box 23)
  - GPSC Subsidy, 1985-1986 (Box 23)
  - Student Activities Fee, 1985-1986 (Box 23)
  - Fee Increase, 1985 (Box 23)
  - Additional Information about Various Policy Issues, 1985-1986 (Box 23)
  - Notes from Norm, 1985-1986 (Box 23)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1985-1986 (Box 23)
  - Film and Video Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 23)
  - Cable 13: General Records, 1985-1986 (Box 23)
  - Cable 13: Programming, 1985 (Box 23)
  - Cable 13: JVC - Cameras, 1985 (Box 23)
  - Cable 13: House O, 1985 (Box 23)
  - Cable 13: Film and Video Center, 1985 (Box 23)
  - Cable 13: Cameron, 1985 (Box 23)
  - Cable 13: Miscellaneous Records, 1986 (Box 23)
  - Special Events Committee: Homecoming, 1985 (Box 23)
  - Vice President for Administration Applications, 1985-1986 (Box 23)
  - Applications [various positions], 1985-1986 (Box 23)
  - Finance: Budget, 1985-1986 (Box 23)
  - Student Organizations, 1985-1986 (Box 23)
  - Budget, 1985-1986 (Box 23)
  - Galleries Committee: General Records, 1985-1986 (Box 23)
  - Galleries Committee: Jack Tilton, 1985-1986 (Box 23)
  - Joan Baez/David Ross Proposal, 1985-1986 (Box 23)
  - American Pictures, 1985-1986 (Box 23)
  - Minutes, various committees, 1985-1986 (Box 23)
  - Broadway at Duke, 1985-1986 (Box 24)
  - Performing Arts Committee: General Records, 1985-1986 (Box 24)
  - South Africa, 1986 (Box 24)
  - Broadway at Duke: "No Shows", 1985-1986 (Box 24)
  - Programming for University Bars: General, 1985-1986 (Box 24)
  - Special Events: General Records, 1985-1986 (Box 24)
  - William Crofut, 1985-1986 (Box 24)
  - Gen. William Westmoreland, September 19, 1985 (Box 24)
  - Symposium on South Africa, October, 85 (Box 24)
  - The Grateful Dead, October 1-2, 1985 (Box 24)
  - Sting, October 5, 1985 (Box 24)
  - UB40, October 16, 1985 (Box 24)
  - David Brenner, October 17, 1985 (Box 24)
  - Homecoming, 1985 (Box 24)
  - Tommy Dorsey, November 2, 1985 (Box 24)
  - Paul Young, November 5, 1985 (Box 24)
  - ISRA Art Productions, 1985-1986 (Box 24)
  - "They're Playin' Our Song", November 14, 1985 (Box 24)
  - David Halberstam, November 19, 1985 (Box 24)
  - North Carolina Boys Choir, December 2, 1985 (Box 24)
  - Hooters, December 5, 1985 (Box 24)
  - Christmas Tree Lighting, 1985 (Box 24)
  - Noises Off, January 17, 1986 (Box 24)
  - "In Concert", March 19, 1986 (Box 24)
  - Video Projection of Championship Game, March 27, 1986 (Box 24)
  - Karen Murphy - David Burns, 1985-1986 (Box 24)
  - Modern English, April 5, 1986 (Box 24)
  - The Romantics, April 5, 1986 (Box 24)
  - Eleanor Smeal, April 10, 1986 (Box 24)
  - BSA & Union: Ain't Misbehavin', 1985-1986 (Box 24)
  - Leonard Nimoy, April 14, 1986 (Box 24)
  - Al McGuire, 1986 (Box 24)
  - Springfest 1986: Tax Forms, 1986 (Box 24)
  - Springfest, 1986 (Box 24)
  - Fashion Symposium, 1986 (Box 24)
  - Summer Programming, 1986 (Box 24)
  - University Union Board Records, 1969-1985 (Box 24)
  - Miscellaneous Policy, 1982-1984 (Box 24)
  - Policies & Constitution, 1973-1986 (Box 24)
  - Proposed Budgets, 1985-1986 (Box 24)
  - DUU President Correspondence (inc. Committee Lists), 1985-1986 (Box 24)
  - Homecoming, Fall 1985 (Box 24)
  - Executive Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 24)
  - Finance, 1985-1986 (Box 24)
  - Major Speakers, 1985-1986 (Box 24)
  - Union Retreat, 1985-1986 (Box 24)
  - Special Events, 1985-1986 (Box 24)
  - Programming, 1985-1986 (Box 24)
  - Policies Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 24)
  - Interaction Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 24)
  - Galleries Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 24)
  - Fashion Symposium, 1986 (Box 24)
  - Miscellaneous Records, 1985-1986 (Box 24)
  - Retreat Agenda, 1986 (Box 24)
  - Facilities Committee: Bryan Center Birthday - 5 years, 1986-1987 (Box 24)
  - Programming Committee: Meetings, 1986-1987 (Box 24)
  - Budget, 1986-1987 (Box 24)
  - Page and Cameron Seating, 1986-1987 (Box 24)
  - Info Desk, 1986-1987 (Box 24)
  - Official Letters, 1986-1987 (Box 24)
  - Provost Agreement, 1986-1987 (Box 24)
  - Committees, 1986-1987 (Box 24)
  - Union Calendar, 1986-1987 (Box 24)
  - WEEDS - deLaurentis, circa 1986 (Box 24)
  - Financial Reports, 1986-1987 (Box 24)
  - International Conference, January 20-21, 1987 (Box 24)
  - Galleries Committee: Rejected Show, 1986 (Box 24)
  - Galleries Committee: Al Frega, September, 1986 (Box 24)
  - Galleries Committee: Noelle Braynard, 1986-1987 (Box 24)
  - Galleries Committee: Susan Woodruff, 1986-1987 (Box 24)
  - Galleries Committee: Richard Karp, 1986-1987 (Box 24)
  - Galleries Committee: Ken Lambert, 1986-1987 (Box 24)
  - Galleries Committee: Clare Leighton, 1986-1987 (Box 24)
  - Galleries Committee: Victor Machuca, October 23-November 24, 1986 (Box 24)
  - Galleries Committee: Indiana University, 1986 (Box 24)
  - Galleries Committee: Joseph Coco, circa 1986 (Box 24)
  - Galleries Committee: Paul Weinberg, September, 1986 (Box 24)
  - Oktoberfest: Tax Agreement Forms, 1986 (Box 24)
  - Springfest: Tax Agreement Forms, 1987 (Box 24)
  - Galleries Committee: Ellen Zahorec, Summer 1986 (Box 24)
  - University Union Board, 1986-1987 (Box 24)
  - Proposals, 1986-1987 (Box 24)
  - Fashion Symposium: Spring, 1986-1987 (Box 24)
  - Miscellaneous Records, 1986 (Box 24)
  - Memos, 1986 (Box 24)
  - NACA, 1986-1987 (Box 24)
  - Facilities, 1986-1987 (Box 24)
  - Special Events, 1986-1987 (Box 24)
  - Miscellaneous Records/Minutes, 1986-1987 (Box 24)
  - Cable 13/Freewater, October 24-25, 1986 (Box 24)
  - Referendum, 1986-1987 (Box 24)
  - Retreat, 1986 (Box 24)
  - Programming Schedule, 1986-1987 (Box 24)
  - Bryan Center Opening, January, 1987 (Box 24)
  - Oriental Festival, February, 1987 (Box 24)
  - Performing Arts Committee: "Ceremonies in Dark Old Men", September 30, 1986 (Box 24)
  - Major Attractions: Branford Marsalis, October 10, 1986 (Box 24)
  - Special Events: Oktoberfest, October, 1986 (Box 24)
  - Programming for University Bars: White Animals/Smash for Cash, October 11, 1987 (Box 24)
  - Major Attractions: Laser Show, October 15, 1986 (Box 24)
  - Programming for University Bars: Barrence Whitfield and the Savages, October 16, 1986 (Box 24)
  - Homecoming 1986, October 25, 1986 (Box 24)
  - Special Events: Blue and White Nite, October 25, 1986 (Box 24)
  - Special Events: Halloween, 1986 (Box 24)
  - Major Attractions: R.E.M. Concert, November 15, 1986 (Box 24)
  - Tree Lighting, December 2, 1986 (Box 24)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Hansel and Gretel, December 2, 1986 (Box 24)
  - Tap Dance Kid, December 4, 1986 (Box 24)
  - Chen and Dancers, January 30, 1987 (Box 24)
  - Chinese New Year, January 30, 1987 (Box 24)
  - Major Attractions: Chicago City Limits, February 11, 1987 (Box 24)
  - Major Attractions: Sam Kinison, February 15, 1987 (Box 24)
  - Major Attractions: Ambassador Arkaby Shevchenko, February 17, 1987 (Box 24)
  - Major Attractions: Hoodo Gurus, February 26, 1987 (Box 24)
  - Bryan Center Birthday, February 27, 1987 (Box 24)
  - Programming for University Bars: The Lyres, March 4, 1987 (Box 24)
  - Springfest, 1987 (Box 24)
  - Major Attractions: Elvis Costello, April 21, 1987 (Box 24)
  - Major Attractions: Biloxi Blues Contract, 1987 (Box 24)
  - Major Attractions: Resolutions, circa 1986 (Box 24)
  - Finance: Budget, 1986-1987 (Box 24)
  - Student Fundraising Policy, circa 1986 (Box 24)
  - Finance: Income Statements, 1986-1987 (Box 24)
  - Finance: General Information, 1985-1986 (Box 25)
  - Applications and Interviews, 1985-1986 (Box 25)
  - Minutes, various committees, 1985-1986 (Box 25)
  - Major Speaker: Miscellaneous/General, 1985-1986 (Box 25)
  - University Union Board: Minutes, etc., 1974-1986 (Box 25)
  - Special Events: Tree Lighting, 1985 (Box 25)
  - Cable 13: General, 1985-1986 (Box 25)
  - Cable 13: Living History Program, 1985-1986 (Box 25)
  - Cable 13: Programming, 1985-1986 (Box 25)
  - Cable 13: PBS, 1985-1986 (Box 25)
  - Cable 13: ASDU, 1985-1986 (Box 25)
  - Cable 13: JVC - Cameras, 1985 (Box 25)
  - Cable 13: PBS, 1986 (Box 25)
  - Cable 13: Video Auditorium, 1985-186 (Box 25)
  - Cable 13: Barbaralee Diamondstein Taped Conversations, circa 1985 (Box 25)
  - Cable 13: Constitution and Inventories, circa 1986 (Box 25)
  - Cable 13: Provost Agreement, 1985-1986 (Box 25)
  - Cable 13: Cable Research, 1982-1986 (Box 25)
  - Cable 13: Articles, 1986 (Box 25)
  - Cable 13: T-shirts, 1985-1986 (Box 25)
  - Cable 13: Interviews Produced by Cable 13, through 1985 (Box 25)
  - Cable 13: Cablecasters, 1985-1986 (Box 25)
  - Cable 13: College Satellite Network, 1985-1986 (Box 25)
  - Programming: Minutes, 1986-1987 (Box 25)
  - Cable 13: Rock World, 1986-1987 (Box 25)
  - Cable 13: Campaign for Cable, 1986 (Box 25)
  - Special Events: Tree Lighting, 1986 (Box 25)
  - Cable 13: CSN, 1986-1987 (Box 25)
  - 1986 Constitutional Revision, 1986 (Box 25)
  - Galleries: Student Shows, 1986-1987 (Box 25)
  - University Union Board: Minutes, etc., 1986-1987 (Box 25)
  - Finance: General Information, 1985-1986 (Box 25)
  - Galleries Committee: Contracts, 1986-1987 (Box 26)
  - Galleries Committee: Sales, 1986-1987 (Box 26)
  - Major Speakers: Budget, 1986-1987 (Box 26)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Advertisers, 1986-1987 (Box 26)
  - Biloxi Blues, 1986-1987 (Box 26)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Broadway at Duke, 1986 (Box 26)
  - Performing Arts Committee: General, 1986-1987 (Box 26)
  - Speidel, Goodrich, and Little, 1986-1987 (Box 26)
  - Programming for University Bars: General, 1986-1987 (Box 26)
  - Yearlook Reference: History, 1986 and 1988 (Box 26)
  - Yearlook Reference Questions: History, 1986 and 1988 (Box 26)
  - Yearlook: Videotape Network, undated (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: Yearlook Reference History, 1986 and 1988 (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: Rock World, 1986-1987 (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: CSN, 1986-1987 (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: Van Repair Estimate, 1986 (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: Slander Insurance, 1986 (Box 26)
  - Historical Yearlook Documents, undated (Box 26)
  - Focus Group Information, undated (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: Cable Crossword Contest, February 28, 1987 (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: Chief Engineer Interviews, March 20, 1987 (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: Athletic Department - Van Renovation Donation (History and Completion), June 29, 1987 (Box 26)
  - Fashion Show, 1987 (Box 26)
  - Performing Arts, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Joint Program Council/Executive Meeting Minutes, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Duke on Display, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Minutes [various committees], 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Union Budget: Final, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Galleries: Press Releases, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Michelle Demanche, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Wenhai Ma, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Interaction Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Major Attractions, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Major Speakers, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Special Events, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Video Yearlook, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: Survey Example, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: Organization/Assignments, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: Long Range Planning, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: Cable Show Proposals, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: Broadcast Schedules, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: Programming, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: Outside Programming Office, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: Special Projects/Documentation, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: Special Events, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: ASDU, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: Video Yearlook, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: Publicity/Advertising, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: SWAN (Emergency Information System), 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: Cable 13 (Tom Houston), 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: Technical, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: Sign-ups and Assignments, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: House O (Room 113) Letter from VP Griffith, July 23, 1987 (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: Cable Reception, September 9, 1987 (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: CSN Sex on Campus, September 30, 1987 (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: CSN American Foreign Policy, October 2, 1987 (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: USB Video, October 3, 1987 (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: ASDU Elections, November 12, 1987 (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: Executive Committee Meetings, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: Lists, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: "A Walk in the Woods" - Commercial, February 3-6, 1988 (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: Reagan Visit, February 8, 1988 (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: CSN Presidential Debates, February 18, 1988 (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: Studio Asbestos Problem, 1988 (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: Equipment use Problem (Paletz), 1988 (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: Bryan Center Move, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: Cable 13 Articles, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: University Governance Committee Report, April 22, 1988 (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: CSN Contract, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: Rockworld Contract, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: Notes, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: Speed Order List, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: Equipment Purchase and Repair, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: Budget, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: 01 Flowers - Renovations, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: Studio Renovations, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: Van Renovations, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: Fundraising, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: Student Run Organizations Report, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: Programming Committee Meeting, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: Union, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: Yearlook Reference, Flyers and Publicity, 1988 (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: Student Run Organizations Problems - SOS MAT, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Cable 13: The Cable 13 Report, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Galleries Committee: Catalina Aroncena, Fall 1987 (Box 26)
  - Galleries Committee: Lynne Saville, Fall 1987 (Box 26)
  - Galleries Committee: Lori Lynn Davis, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Galleries Committee: Elaine Ellman, Fall 1987 (Box 26)
  - Galleries Committee: Theresa Rhyne, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Galleries Committee: "3 From 72", 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Galleries Committee: Hunt Slonem, Fall 1987 (Box 26)
  - Galleries Committee: Andy McLawhorn, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Galleries Committee: Video Visions, Fall 1987 (Box 26)
  - Galleries Committee: Judge Gallery Masters, Fall 1987 (Box 26)
  - Galleries Committee: The JP Natkin Gallery, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - President's Notes on Facilities, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Policy, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Presidental Applications, 1987 (Box 26)
  - Summer Enrichment Program, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Finance, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - NACA, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Yearlook: Cable 13 Referendum, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Symposium: Media, Film, Video, etc. Symposium Notes, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Symposium: Rejected Ideas, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Long Range Planning, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Marine Lab (Beaufort): Informational Booklet, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - DAC: Centerfest, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Freewater Troubles, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Alumni Response, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Women's Task Force, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Young Trustee, 1987 (Box 26)
  - Young Trustee Selection, 1988 (Box 26)
  - Surveys and Analysis, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Stop Card Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Quad Squad, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Dr. Brodie Correspondence, 1988 (Box 26)
  - Craft Center, 1988 (Box 26)
  - Correspondence (Debbie Queen Files), 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Student Activism, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Finance: Budget, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Final Report Concerning Student-Run Organizations, 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Galleries: William Campbell, 1988 (Box 27)
  - Galleries: Carol Doenecke, 1988 (Box 27)
  - Galleries: Miscellaneous/General, 1987-1988 (Box 27)
  - Galleries: Schedule, 1987-1988 (Box 27)
  - Galleries: Nancy Pierson, April 20-May 29, 1987 (Box 27)
  - Galleries: Shirley and David Rowen, May 6-August 15, 1987 (Box 27)
  - Galleries: Andy McLawhorn, July 3-August 15, 1987 (Box 27)
  - Galleries: Judge Gallery, August 29-September 24, 1987 (Box 27)
  - Galleries: Catalina Aroncena, September 8-October 10, 1987 (Box 27)
  - Galleries: Hunt Slonem, September 26-October 24, 1987 (Box 27)
  - Galleries: Lynn Saville, October 10-November 13, 1987 (Box 27)
  - Galleries: Diana Cull, Kate Feterolf, and Anne Was, November 14-December 11, 1987 (Box 27)
  - Galleries: Elaine Ellman, November 20, 1987-January 3, 1988 (Box 27)
  - Galleries: Jones and Theilgard, January 9-February 6, 1988 (Box 27)
  - Galleries: Theresa Marie Rhyne, January 16-February 13, 1988 (Box 27)
  - Galleries: Michel DeManche, January 30-March 4, 1988 (Box 27)
  - Galleries: Wen Hai Ma, February 14-March 12, 1988 (Box 27)